AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5478
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XXIII: National Rules and Working Conditions Agreements Between Employees Represented by the Railway Employees Department of the AFL and Carriers Under the Provisions of the Transportation Act of 1920 - Correspondence, Etc., 1920-1934
  - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 78)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 121, Folder 79)
    Code No. MC-153-14A-146; May 26, 1921 - Jun. 5, 1922
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 121, Folder 80)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 121, Folder 81)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 121, Folder 82)
  - Vermont Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 83)
  - Western Railway of Atlanta, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 84)
    Aug. 3-6
  - Washington and Vandemere Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 85)
    Code No. MC-2-14A-96; Aug. 10, 1921 - Sept. 21, 1921
  - Wadley Southern Railway, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 86)
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 87)
    Code No. MC-189-14A-120; May 17, 1921 - Oct. 26, 1921
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 88)
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 89)
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 90)
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 91)
  - Wyoming and Northwestern Railway, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 92)
    Code No. MC-25-14A-64; Aug. 18, 1921 - Sept. 22, 1921
  - Wichita Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 93)
    Aug. 6, 1921 - Sept. 22, 1921
  - Watertown and Sioux Falls Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 94)
    Code No. MC-442-14A-34; May 6, 1921 - Jun. 21, 1921
  - Weatherford, Mineral Wells and Northwestern Railway (Box 121, Folder 95)
  - Washington and Southern Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 96)
    Aug. 4-18
  - York Harbor and Beach Railroad, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 97)
  - Yazoo and Mississippi Valley, 1921 (Box 121, Folder 98)
    Code No. MC-446-14A-174; Jun. 16
  - St. Louis, Troy and Eastern Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Code No. MC-166-14-A-154; May 24, 1921 - Dec. 18, 1922
  - St. Louis, Troy and Eastern Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - St. Paul Bridge and Terminal Company, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Code No. MC-452-14A-200; Jul. 19, 1921 - Aug. 19, 1921
  - St. Paul Union Depot Company, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Code No. MC-414-14A-42; May 7, 1921 - Aug. 5, 1921
  - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Code No. MC-169-14A-19; May 2, 1921 - Jan. 6, 1922
  - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    Code No. MC-169-14A-19-1; Jun. 18, 1921 - Sept. 30, 1921
  - Trans-Mississippi Terminal Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    Code No. MC-170-14A-91; May 17, 1921 - Aug. 4, 1921
  - Tennessee Central Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    Code No. MC-174-14A-190; Jun. 28, 1921 - May 9, 1922
  - Texas Midland Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    Code No. MC-172-14A-139; May 27, 1921 - Oct. 13, 1921
  - Toledo, Saginaw and Muskegon Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Texarkana and Fort Smith Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    Code No. MC-462-14A-218; Aug. 4, 1921 - Sept. 26, 1921
  - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    Code No. MC-178-14A-195; Jul. 13, 1921 - Oct. 22, 1921
  - Toledo Terminal Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    Code No. MC-386-14A-86; May 16, 1921 - Jan. 10, 1922
  - Toledo, St. Louis and Western Railroad (Clover Leaf Railroad), 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    Code No. MC-173-14A-148; May 30, 1921 - Jul. 4, 1922
  - Toledo, St. Louis and Western Railroad (Clover Leaf Railroad), 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Toledo, St. Louis and Western Railroad (Clover Leaf Railroad), 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Toledo, St. Louis and Western Railroad (Clover Leaf Railroad), 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Toledo, St. Louis and Western Railroad (Clover Leaf Railroad), 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Tacoma Eastern Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - Toledo and Ohio Central Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    Code No. MC-181-14A-103; May 19, 1921 - Mar. 10, 1922
  - Toledo and Ohio Central Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - Toledo and Ohio Central Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - Toledo and Ohio Central Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 28)
    Code No. MC-171-14A-137; May 25, 1921 - Nov. 13, 1921
  - Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 29)
  - Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 30)
  - Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 32)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 33)
    Code No. MC-182-14A-4
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 34)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 35)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 36)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 37)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 38)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 39)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 40)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 41)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 42)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 43)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 44)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 45)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 46)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 47)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 48)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 49)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 50)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 51)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 52)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 53)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 54)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 55)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 56)
  - Union Stock Yards of Omaha, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 57)
    Code No. MC-465-14A-220; Aug. 3, 1921 - Sept. 30, 1921
  - Union Railway Company, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 58)
    Code No. MC-432-14A-116; May 21, 1921 - Aug. 2, 1921
  - Ulster and Delaware Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 59)
    Code No. MC-385-14A-179; Jun. 21, 1921 - Sept. 23, 1921
  - United States and Canada Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 60)
  - Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 61)
    Code No. MC-216-14A-181; Jun. 17, 1921 - Dec. 10, 1921
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 62)
    Code No. MC-232-14A-77; May 13, 1921 - Jul. 6, 1922
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 63)
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 64)
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 65)
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 66)
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 67)
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 68)
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 69)
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 70)
  - Virginian Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 122, Folder 71)
  - Washington Terminal System, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 72)
    Code No. MC-186-14A-182; Jun. 4, 1921 - Aug. 19, 1921
  - West Side Belt Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 73)
    Aug. 3
  - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 74)
    Code No. MC-190-14A-138; May 24, 1921 - Sept. 9, 1921
  - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 75)
  - Winston and Salem Southbound Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 76)
    Code No. MC-466-14A-221; Aug. 4, 1921 - Nov. 2, 1921
  - Wabash Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 77)
    Code No. MC-184-14A-53; May 11, 1921
  - Wabash Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 78)
  - Wabash Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 79)
  - Western Maryland Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 80)
    Code No. MC-187-14A-57; May 10, 1921 - Aug. 25, 1921
  - Western Maryland Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 81)
  - Western Maryland Railroad, 1921 (Box 122, Folder 82)
- Series XXIV: 14B Files
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), affidavits, minutes, clippings, circulars, lists of employees (for seniority representation, voting, etc.) regarding contract negotiations; amending the contract rules; supplemental agreements to contracts; assignin
  - Ft. Dodge, Des Moines & Southern Railway (Box 123, Folder 1)
    14B-3
  - Baltimore & Ohio, Chicago Railroad (Box 123, Folder 2)
    14B-4
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railway (Box 123, Folder 3)
    14B-7
  - Canadian National Railway (Box 123, Folder 4)
    14B-8
  - Canadian National Railway (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad (Box 124, Folder 2)
    14B-9
  - New York Central Transport Co. (Box 125, Folder 1)
    14B-11
  - Alabama & Great Southern Railroad (Box 125, Folder 2)
    14B-13
  - Chicago & Northwestern Railway (Box 125, Folder 3)
    14B-17
  - Chicago & Northwestern Railway (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad (Box 126, Folder 2)
    14B-18
  - New Orleans Great Northern (Box 126, Folder 3)
    14B-19
  - Tennessee Central Railway (Box 126, Folder 4)
    14B-23
  - Chicago Great Western Railway (Box 126, Folder 5)
    14B-28
  - Clinchfield Railroad (Box 126, Folder 6)
    14B-29
  - Seaboard Air Line Railroad (Box 126, Folder 7)
    14B-34
  - Contracting out by Railroad, etc., and Jurisdictional Agreements and Correspondence (Box 127, Folder 1)
    14B-37
  - Contracting out by Railroad, etc., and Jurisdictional Agreements and Correspondence (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Contracting out by Railroad, etc., and Jurisdictional Agreements and Correspondence (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Cincinnati Union Terminal Co. (Box 130, Folder 1)
    14B-116
  - Central of Georgia Railway (Box 130, Folder 2)
    14B-124
  - Spokane, Portland & Seattle Railway (Box 130, Folder 3)
    14B-127
  - Florida East Coast Railway (Box 130, Folder 4)
    14B-131
  - Illinois Central Railroad (Box 130, Folder 5)
    14B-132
  - Missouri, Kansas Texas Railroad (Box 130, Folder 6)
    14B-135
  - Missouri, Kansas Texas Railroad (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Georgia & Florida Railroad (Box 131, Folder 2)
    14B-136
  - Charleston & Western Carolina Railway (Box 131, Folder 3)
    14B-137
  - Northwestern Pacific Railroad (Box 131, Folder 4)
    14B-138
  - Illinois Terminal Railroad (Box 131, Folder 5)
    14B-139
  - Boston & Maine Railroad (Box 131, Folder 6)
    14B-140
  - Boston & Maine Railroad (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Electric Railway (Box 132, Folder 2)
    14B-141
  - Virginian Railroad (Box 132, Folder 3)
    14B-142
  - Norfolk & Western Railway (Box 132, Folder 4)
    14B-143
  - Union Pacific Railroad (Box 133, Folder 1)
    14B-144
  - Denver & Rio Grande Western Railroad (Box 133, Folder 2)
    14B-147
  - Main Central Railroad (Box 133, Folder 3)
    14B-149
  - Detroit, Toledo & Ironton Railroad (Box 133, Folder 4)
    14B-150
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Co. of Texas (Box 133, Folder 5)
    14B-152
  - Southern Pacific (Pacific Lines) (Box 134, Folder 1)
    14B-153
  - Southern Pacific (Pacific Lines) (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad (Box 135, Folder 2)
    14B-156
  - Atlanta & West Point Railroad (Box 135, Folder 3)
    14B-162
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad (Box 136, Folder 1)
    14B-188
  - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway (Box 136, Folder 2)
    14B-252
  - Gulf, Colorado & Santa FE Railway (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 136, Folder 4)
    14B-258
  - Pennsylvania-Reading Seashore Lines (Box 137, Folder 1)
    14B-267
  - Contracting out by Railroad, etc., and Jurisdictional Agreements and Correspondence (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Louisville & Nashville Railroad (Box 138, Folder 1)
    14B-283
  - Contracting out by Railroad, etc., and Jurisdictional Agreements and Correspondence (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Contracting out by Railroad, etc., and Jurisdictional Agreements and Correspondence (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago & St, Louis Railway (Big Four) (Box 140, Folder 1)
    14B-39
  - Erie Railroad (Box 140, Folder 2)
    14B-40
  - Elgin, Joliet & Easter Railway (Box 140, Folder 3)
    14B-48
  - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad (Box 140, Folder 4)
    14B-57
  - Hudson & Manhattan Railroad (Box 140, Folder 5)
    14B-75
  - Louisiana & Arkansas Railway (Box 141, Folder 1)
    14B-78
  - Soo Line Railroad (Box 141, Folder 2)
    14B-98
  - Chicago & Illinois Midland Railway (Box 141, Folder 3)
    14B-109
  - Toledo, Peoria & Western Railroad (Box 141, Folder 4)
    14B-110
  - Railroad Retirement Boards (Box 142, Folder 1)
    14B-1-23 through 14B-281-23
  - Toledo, Peoria & Western Railroad (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific Railroad (Box 143, Folder 2)
    14B-164
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Gulf, Colorado & Santa FE Railway (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railway (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Chicago & Northwestern Railway (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Monon Railroad (Box 144, Folder 3)
    14B-44
  - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Soo Line Railroad (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Illinois Central Railroad (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Missouri, Kansas Texas Railroad (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Union Pacific Railroad (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Rutland Railway (Box 145, Folder 1)
    14B-240
  - Philadelphia, Reading and Pottsville. Teleg. (Box 145, Folder 2)
    14B-242
  - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Gulf, Colorado & Santa FE Railway (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific Railroad (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Texas & New Orleans Railroad (Box 146, Folder 2)
    14B-167
  - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad (Box 146, Folder 3)
    14B-169
  - Denver & Rio Grande Western Railroad (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Kansas City Terminal Railway (Box 147, Folder 2)
    14B-184
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Portland Terminal Co. (Box 147, Folder 4)
    14B-194
  - Duluth, Missabe & Iron Range Railway (Box 148, Folder 1)
    14B-198
  - Bingham and Garfield Railroad (Box 148, Folder 2)
    14B-205
  - Mystic Terminal Co. (Box 148, Folder 3)
    14B-209
  - Wabash Railroad (Box 148, Folder 4)
    14B-233
  - Rutland Railway (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Shreveport Joint Car Inspection and Interchange Bureau (Box 149, Folder 1)
    14B-254
  - Bessemer & Lake Erie Railroad (Box 149, Folder 2)
    14B-255
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Great Northern Railway Co. (Box 153, Folder 1)
    14B-263
  - Louisville & Nashville Railroad (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - St. Louis - San Francisco Railway (Box 153, Folder 3)
    14B-322
  - St. Louis - San Francisco Railway (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia, Bethlehem & New England Railroad (Box 154, Folder 2)
    14B-324
  - Pullman Co. (Box 154, Folder 3)
    14B-365
  - Pullman Co. (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Contracting out by Railroad, etc., and Jurisdictional Agreements and Correspondence (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Pullman Co. (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Terminal Railway Alabama State Docks (Box 156, Folder 3)
    14B-374
  - Contracting out by Railroad, etc., and Jurisdictional Agreements and Correspondence (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Boston & Maine Railroad (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal (Box 157, Folder 4)
    14B-391
- Series IIIb: Organizing, 1918-1954
  - Alaska Railroad, 1925-1963 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-297
- Series IVb: International Organizations, American Federation of Labor - Union Affiliated with the AFL, 1912-1961
  - Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, 1928-1962 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    Code No. 16-1, pt. 1; June 29, 1928 - Jan. 10, 1962; See also Box 13
  - Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, 1963-1964 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    Code No. 16-1, pt. 2; Feb. 7, 1963 - Sept. 3, 1964; See also Box 13
  - Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, 1964-1966 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    Code No. 16-1, pt. 3; Dec. 22, 1964 - Aug. 30, 1966; See also Box 13
  - Carmen, 1946-1963 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    Code No. 16-2, pt. 2; Jan. 15, 1946 - Jun. 21, 1963; See also Box 13
  - Machinists, 1946-1966 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    Code No. 16-8, pt. 2; May 8, 1946 - Jun. 6, 1966; See also Box 13
  - Boilermakers, 1956-1963 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    Code No. 16-9, pt. 3; Jan. 4, 1956 - Jul. 12, 1963; See also Box 13
  - Mine Workers, 1922-1959 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    Code No. 16-11, pt. 1; Jan. 31, 1922 - Apr. 29, 1959; See also Box 13
  - Firemen and Oilers, 1922-1965 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    Code No. 16-13, pt. 1; Feb. 8, 1922 - Jun. 2, 1965; See also Box 13
  - Electrical Workers, 1946-1966 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    Code No. 16-15, pt. 2; Jun. 19, 1946 - May 12, 1966; See also Box 13
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1926-1962 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    Code No. 16-20, pt. 1; Aug. 16, 1926 - Aug. 20, 1962; See also Box 13
  - Railroad Telegraphers, 1927-1962 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    Code No. 16-21, pt. 1; Apr. 21, 1927 - Nov. 2, 1962; See also Box 13
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1933-1963 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    Code No. 16-22, pt. 1; Aug. 15, 1933 - Oct. 30, 1963; See also Box 13
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1929-1963 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    Code No. 16-23, pt. 1; Dec. 2, 1929 - Jun. 30, 1963; See also Box 13
- Series Vb: American Federation of Labor, Departments Other Than This Department and State Federations of Labor, 1941-1968
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1961-1962 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 10; Apr. 26, 1961 - Apr. 30, 1962; See also Box 13
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1962-1964 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 11; Jul. 16, 1962 - Aug. 28, 1964; See also Box 13
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1964-1966 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 12; Sept. 11, 1964 - Dec. 8, 1966; See also Box 13
  - AFL - Other Departments, 1967-1968 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    Code No. 17-1, pt. 13; Jan. 9, 1967 - Dec. 19, 1968; See also Box 13
- Series VIIb: American Federation of Railway Workers and Other Outside Organizations - Not Affiliated with the American Federation of Labor, 1927-1953
  - American Railway Supervisors Association, 1943-1965 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    Code No. 20-33, pt. 3; Jan. 21, 1943 - Sept. 22, 1965; See also Box 14
- Series VIIIb: System Federations and Matters Pertaining to Individual System Federations, 1917-1961
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1941-1960 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    Code No. 22-2, pt. 2; Jun. 11, 1941 - Nov. 21, 1960; See also Box 16
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1961-1966 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    Code No. 22-2, pt. 3; Jan. 11, 1961 - Apr. 15, 1966; See also Box 16
  - Kansas City Southern Railway, 1920-1966 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    Code No. 22-3; Dec. 12, 1920 - Apr. 15, 1966; See also Box 16
  - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad, 1953-1964 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    Code No. 22-6, pt. 4; Mar. 5, 1953 - Dec. 28, 1964; See also Box 16
  - Northern Pacific Railway, 1940-1962 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    Code No. 22-7, pt. 2; Jan. 7, 1940 - May 21, 1962; See also Box 16
  - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railway, 1926-1961 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    Code No. 22-8, pt. 1; Apr. 21, 1926 - Aug. 1, 1961; See also box 16
  - Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad, 1941-1964 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    Code No. 22-10, pt. 2; Nov. 4, 1941 - Dec. 15, 1964; See also box 16
  - Wabash Railroad, 1927-1961 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    Code No. 22-13, pt. 1; Jan. 17, 1927 - Oct. 25, 1961; See also Box 16
  - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1958-1966 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    Code No. 22-16, pt. 2; Jan. 13, 1958 - Dec. 1, 1966; See also Box 16
  - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1951-1963 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    Code No. 22-17, pt. 2; May 7, 1951 - Aug. 27, 1963; See also box 16
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1947-1964 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    Code No. 22-20, pt. 2; Dec. 27, 1947 - Jun. 30, 1964; See also box 17
  - Southern Railway, 1923-1964 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    Code No. 22-21, pt. 2; Nov. 9, 1923 - Aug. 18, 1964; See also box 17
  - The Frisco - St. Louis-San Francisco Railroad, 1943-1963 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    Code No. 22-22, pt. 1; Mar. 10, 1943 - Oct. 14, 1963; See also box 17
  - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, 1939-1960 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    Code No. 22-23; Dec. 30, 1939 - Mar. 30, 1960; See also box 17
  - New York, Ontario and Western Railway, 1937-1959 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    Code No. 22-31, pt. 1; Oct. 8, 1937 - Jun. 10, 1959; See also box 17
  - Seaboard Airline Railroad, 1956-1966 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    Code No. 22-39, pt. 3; Jan. 16, 1956 - Dec. 30, 1966; See also box 18
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1943-1953 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    Code No. 22-41, pt. 5; Dec. 28, 1943 - Dec. 28, 1953; See also box 18
  - Big Four - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway, 1941-1964 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    Code No. 22-54, pt. 2; Jan. 7, 1941 - Dec. 15, 1964
  - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1941-1964 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    Code No. 22-69, pt. 2; Dec. 9, 1941 - Nov. 17, 1964; See also box 19
  - Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railway, 1938-1964 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    Code No. 22-71, pt. 1; Apr. 29, 1938 - May 5, 1964; See also box 19
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad, 1958-1964 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    Code No. 22-76, pt. 5; Jan. 16, 1958 - Dec. 16, 1964; See also box 19
  - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad, 1944-1963 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    Code No. 22-78, pt. 2; Dec. 30, 1944 - Mar. 8, 1963; See also box 19
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1950-1965 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    Code No. 22-91, pt. 2; Dec. 26, 1950 - Dec. 29, 1965; See also box 20
  - Grand Trunk Western Railroad, 1953-1963 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    Code No. 22-92, pt. 3; Jan. 8, 1953 - Sept. 16, 1963; See also box 20
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad, 1948-1963 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    Code No. 22-95, pt. 3; Dec. 24, 1948 - Dec. 16, 1963; See also box 20
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, 1954-1964 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    Code No. 22-97, pt. 3; Dec. 20, 1954 - Jul. 6, 1964; See also box 20
  - Erie-Lackawanna Railroad, 1947-1965 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    Code No. 22-100, pt. 7; Jan. 2, 1947 - Dec. 30, 1965; See also box 21
  - Great Northern Railway, 1953-1963 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    Code No. 22-101, pt. 3; Jan. 29, 1953 - Apr. 19, 1963; See also box 21
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1960-1965 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    Code No. 22-105, pt. 5; Jan. 4, 1960 - Jun. 6, 1965; See also box 21
  - Atlanta Joint Terminal Railroad, 1919-1964 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    Code No. 22-110, pt. 1; Mar. 21, 1919 - Sept. 3, 1964; See also box 21
  - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1959-1964 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    Code No. 22-114, pt. 7; Jan. 12, 1959 - Dec. 8, 1964; See also box 21
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1948-1965 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    Code No. 22-117, pt. 3; Jan. 9, 1948 - Dec. 20, 1965; See also box 21
  - Atlanta and West Point and Western Railway of Alabama, 1924-1964 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    Code No. 22-126, pt. 1; Jan. 9, 1924 - Dec. 15, 1964; See also box 21
  - Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway, 1921-1958 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    Code No. 22-128, pt. 1; Apr. 6, 1921 - Dec. 30, 1958; See also box 21